<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Examples on Hugo wodpress</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Examples on Hugo wodpress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/examples/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Example 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-1/</guid>
      <description>Home Referencing Topic sentences A well-written paragraph contains a topic sentence. A topic sentence controls the main idea discussed in a paragraph. It provides the reader with a summary of the key idea and the point of view the writer is expressing. It is often the first sentence as it acts as an introduction to what follows, making it easier for the reader to follow.&#xA;Transcript‘he loves me he loves me not’ is written 21,319 times which represents the number of days I have lived and asked this question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-2/</guid>
      <description>Home Referencing Quoting When you are researching a topic, sometimes you want to include the exact words of another author or speaker in your own work. Using someone’s words in their original form is called quoting, or including a direct quote.&#xA;When to quote Quoting is the way to include the exact words of others in our own work. You might want to use a quote when the specific words that an author or speaker has used are important, such as when someone offers a new definition for a term or presents a new theory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-3/</guid>
      <description>Home Assessments Getting started with assignments Develop your search strategy Choose valid sources Integrating ideas with reporting words Not all information is created equal.&#xA;When you choose information for your assignments, there should be a continual evaluation process occurring. Evaluate information for its relevance and usefulness to your work, and its quality.&#xA;Not all information that is published is credible and reliable, especially if you find that information on the web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-4/</guid>
      <description>HomeAssessmentsReflective writing&#x9;Test Yourself: Sustainable Development Goals quiz View the different structural parts of each example across a number of artists working in different mediums and media.&#xA;Short artist statement - 47 words A short artist statement which captures the visual style and impact of this creative work in an informal yet bold text.&#xA;@gun_shy_design&#xA;#texturalintercourse&#xA;Mixed media installation&#xA;RMIT University Gallery&#xA;#texturalintercourse is a magnificent, OTT, tongue in cheek, contemporary, psychedelic, psycho-sexual journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/examples/example-5/</guid>
      <description>HomeAssessmentsReflective writing&#x9;How to use DIEP (Describe Interpret Evaluate Plan) If you don&amp;#8217;t know how to start writing your artist statement, mind mapping words and ideas that relate to your creative practice is a good way to visualise concepts and create relationships between them.&#xA;Mind mapping activity This activity is best done on paper, however, if you have a mobile device with a drawing app, you can create a digital version in the same way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
