<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Activities on Hugo wodpress</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/activity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Activities on Hugo wodpress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/activity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artist Statement Artwork</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/activity/artist-statement-artwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/activity/artist-statement-artwork/</guid>
      <description>Steven Rendall&#xA;Recent Developments I, 2018&#xA;This is one of 3 works titled Recent Developments: In making these works I was trying to mesh personal conditions and interests to requirements of contemporary painting. This obviously set up a vast array of problems, discrepancies and diversions. The way through this was to hold on to the idea that these paintings could be images of demons. In many cultures a demon is a hybridised creature made up from the components of other creatures – a kind of horrifically meshed collage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Artist Statement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/activity/short-artist-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/activity/short-artist-statement/</guid>
      <description>@gun_shy_design&#xA;#texturalintercourse&#xA;Mixed media installation&#xA;RMIT University Gallery&#xA;#texturalintercourse is a magnificent, OTT, tongue in cheek, contemporary, psychedelic, psycho-sexual journey. A pop subversion exploring fetish in the everyday normality of life. It’s a mad world out there&amp;hellip; Who knows what’s really on people’s minds or behind closed doors?&amp;hellip; Interact with our piece and hashtag #texturalintercourse lovers.&#xA;Thanks to @honchodisko and all the beauties at the 200th Birthday who wrote on our toilet wall lining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short Artist Statement Video</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/activity/short-artist-statement-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/activity/short-artist-statement-video/</guid>
      <description>Keith W Clancy&#xA;BLACK WHOLE (RMX), 2019&#xA;RMIT University Gallery&#xA;BLACK WHOLE (RMX) restages an imaginary cabaret performed by an unidentified Officer: he is at once a ghost, a dream and a traumatic symptom.&#xA;Richard Strauss’s opera Ariadne auf Naxos (1916) acts as a self-nesting framework for this meta-fictional allegory about art, sex, death and childhood. Against the silent commentary of old master paintings, arias by Handel and Vivaldi are ‘mistranslated’ by texts adapted from Octave Mirbeau’s ‘The Torture Garden’ (1899).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
